http://www.wingscenter.com/privacy-policy

GYMNASTICS PROGRAMS
Gymnastics for ages Walking to 4 Years (Boys & Girls)
Gymnastics for Girls Ages 5 and Older
Gymnastics for Boys Ages 5 and Older
Hot Shots Gymnastics (Girls ages 3 to 6 – By invite only)
HOME/
ATHLETICS/SPORTS INSTRUCTIONSWIM LESSONGYMNASTICS PROGRAMSGymnastics for ages Walking to 4 Years (Boys & Girls)Gymnastics for Girls Ages 5 and OlderGymnastics for Boys Ages 5 and OlderHot Shots Gymnastics (Girls ages 3 to 6 – By invite only)Girls Competitive GymnasticsWings Warriors for Boys and Girls ages 5 to 10Challenge MeetsMotor Development
CHILD CARE/Childcare & EducationBefore and After Kindergarten CareBefore and After School CareAll-Day ChildcareTrack Break, School-Day-Out, DayCampsHoliday DaycampParenting the Love and Logic Way
ENTERTAINMENT/EntertainmentPlanet Kid Indoor Soft PlaygroundBirthday PartiesRock ClimbingTeam BuildingField Trip FUNParents Night OutGroup Overnighters and SleepoversElementary School Fundraisers
ABOUT/Who We ArePrivacy PolicyEMPLOYMENT
Contact/
Blog/
where dreams take flight...
Privacy Policy
HOME/
ATHLETICS/SPORTS INSTRUCTIONSWIM LESSONGYMNASTICS PROGRAMSGymnastics for ages Walking to 4 Years (Boys & Girls)Gymnastics for Girls Ages 5 and OlderGymnastics for Boys Ages 5 and OlderHot Shots Gymnastics (Girls ages 3 to 6 – By invite only)Girls Competitive GymnasticsWings Warriors for Boys and Girls ages 5 to 10Challenge MeetsMotor Development
CHILD CARE/Childcare & EducationBefore and After Kindergarten CareBefore and After School CareAll-Day ChildcareTrack Break, School-Day-Out, DayCampsHoliday DaycampParenting the Love and Logic Way
ENTERTAINMENT/EntertainmentPlanet Kid Indoor Soft PlaygroundBirthday PartiesRock ClimbingTeam BuildingField Trip FUNParents Night OutGroup Overnighters and SleepoversElementary School Fundraisers
ABOUT/Who We ArePrivacy PolicyEMPLOYMENT
Contact/
Blog/
Privacy Policy
Protecting Your Privacy is important to the Wings Center and our Staff. We want you to understand what information we collect and how that information is used. In order to provide our customers with a broad range of services as effectively and conveniently as possible, we use technology to manage and maintain customer information. The following policy notice serves as a standard for all Wings Center employees for collection, use, retention and security of nonpublic personal information.What Information We Collect – We collect “nonpublic personal information” in connection with providing a service or product to you. For example, nonpublic personal information includes information regarding your account balance, payment history and overdraft history, if any. We may collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: information we receive from you on registration forms and application forms, information about your transactions with us or others, and information that we receive from third parties.What Information We Disclose – We may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to third parties, such as sub-contractors who depend on accurate financial information to service your account. This might include Collection Agencies, should collection efforts become necessary. We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you to government entities in response to subpoenas, and to credit bureaus. We do NOT disclose any nonpublic personal information about you to anyone except as permitted by law. Wings Center will adhere to this Privacy Policy to former as well as current customers.Our Security Procedures – We also take steps to safeguard customer information. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your nonpublic personal information. If you have any questions in regards to our policy, or would like a copy of the policy, please contact us.
Wings Center Information1875 Century Way.
Boise, ID
83709(208) 376-3641Find Us on FacebookWings Business Office HoursMon - Thur:
8:30am to 8:00pmFriday:
8:30am to 6:00pmSaturday:
8:30am to 12:15pmSunday:
ClosedPlanet Kid Hours (subject to change)Mon – Thur:
9:00am to 6:00pmFri – Sat:
9:00am to 7:00pmSunday:
11:00am to 5:00pm* please note: we are closed the following major US holidays: Easter, Memorial Day, July Fourth, Labor Day, Thanksgiving, Christmas
Wings Center | 1875 Century Way, Boise, ID 83709 | 208-376-3641 | © 2019 Wings, Inc. | All Rights Reserved
